<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://actlab-genesys.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://actlab-genesys.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-01-24T22:11:45+00:00</updated><id>https://actlab-genesys.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">GeneSys</title><subtitle>A programmable deep learning acceleration system generator. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the GeneSys Design Blog</title><link href="https://actlab-genesys.github.io/blog/2025/introduction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the GeneSys Design Blog"/><published>2025-01-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-01-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://actlab-genesys.github.io/blog/2025/introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://actlab-genesys.github.io/blog/2025/introduction/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="welcome-to-the-genesys-design-blog">Welcome to the GeneSys Design Blog</h1> <p>I am excited to introduce the <strong>GeneSys Blog</strong>, a dedicated space where the team will provide updates and tutorials on GeneSys. Whether you are an experienced researcher, an industry professional, or just getting started with GeneSys, this blog will serve as a resource to help you stay informed and engaged.</p> <h2 id="why-start-a-blog-now">Why Start a Blog Now?</h2> <p>As GeneSys continues to evolve, we recognize the importance of sharing our progress with the community. This blog will serve as a platform to:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Provide Updates:</strong> Stay informed on the latest enhancements, optimizations, and design changes in GeneSys. We will share insights into our ongoing research and development efforts.</li> <li><strong>Offer Tutorials and Exercises:</strong> Whether you are new to GeneSys or looking to deepen your understanding, our blog will feature hands-on guides, practical exercises, and example applications to help you make the most of our architecture.</li> <li><strong>Engage with the Community:</strong> We aim to foster an open dialogue by sharing our findings and listening to your feedback, questions, and ideas.</li> </ul> <p>We invite you to <strong>follow</strong> and <strong>contribute</strong> to the conversation as we continue our journey of reimagining acceleration with GeneSys.</p> <p><strong>— Chris</strong></p>]]></content><author><name>Christopher Priebe</name></author><category term="posts"/><category term="announcement"/><category term="introduction"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the GeneSys Design Blog]]></summary></entry></feed>